accommodationdirectory.org 2011-03-14

# Privacy Policy :: Lodging Directory

| 

VacationRental-BO.com is serious about protecting the privacy of our contributers. We use information collected about you only to process and bill orders and to make our Web site a more useful and valuable service. We respect the privacy of those who visit or become advertisers. Our privacy policy is stated below, but please be aware that should you follow a link on our Web site to another Web site, you are no longer covered by this policy. It's a good idea to understand the privacy policy of any Web site before sharing personal information with it.

All personal information is stored on a secure server. We do not store credit card numbers or identifying information on any VacationRental-BO.com server. All such information is stored by PAYPAL, our credit card processing partner, on their secured servers, and is protected via its proprietary methods.  
Your information is not shared with third parties, except:  
1) in the case of special promotions by VacationRental-BO.com, or one of its partners, about which you've requested to be notified;  
2) where a third party performs services on behalf of VacationRental-BO.com and has agreed to keep such information confidential (such as the processing of your credit card payment for example).

NewslettersAs an advertiser or visitor to VacationRental-BO.com, you may receive our newsletters. You may cancel your subscription to these newsletters at any time.

Cookies A "cookie" is a small piece of information sent by a Web server to store in a Web browser so that it can later be read back from that browser. VacationRental-BO.com may use cookies to store some personal preferences for your future visits. Cookies allow us to recognize you more quickly; therefore, your time spent on our site can be more personalized and productive. You'll find that cookies are an industry standard and are used at most major Web sites in much the same way we use them here at VacationRental-BO.com.

We use third-party site usage tracking companies to analyze your Web site visit. In the course of serving our pages, these third parties may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to VacationRental-BO.com and other Web sites in order to help us understand how to serve you better.

By using our Web site and signing up for VacationRental-BO.com services, you consent to the collection and use of the previously mentioned information by VacationRental-BO.com and our affiliates. This policy is subject to change without notice. Privacy issues represent a growing concern for all Web users. To keep up-to-date with our policies, please check this page frequently. We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time.

|   
---|---|---
